{
  "LevelId": 36,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 366,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "HEALTHCARE",
      "question": "improvement of people's physical and mental well-being, providing medical services, treatment"
    },
    {
      "id": 367,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BACKGROUND",
      "question": "commonly used to describe the personal, professional, or historical information"
    },
    {
      "id": 368,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "DAZZLEMENT",
      "question": "word is used to describe the state of being intensely impressed, captivated,"
    },
    {
      "id": 369,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BUCKJUMPER",
      "question": "term is used for a horse that has a tendency to jump high"
    },
    {
      "id": 370,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "AIRSTRIKES",
      "question": "In military operations, term is used to describe the delivery of bombs or missiles from aircraft,"
    },
    {
      "id": 371,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "ACTIVITIES",
      "question": "term encompasses various actions, tasks, or pursuits"
    },
    {
      "id": 372,
      "level_image": 8,
      "answer_text": "ASTRONOMER",
      "question": "profession involves the study of celestial objects, such as stars, planets,"
    },
    {
      "id": 373,
      "level_image": 8,
      "answer_text": "BILLBOARDS",
      "question": "large outdoor advertising structures,"
    },
    {
      "id": 374,
      "level_image": 8,
      "answer_text": "ATTANDANCE",
      "question": "term is commonly used to refer to the presence of individuals"
    },
    {
      "id": 375,
      "level_image": 8,
      "answer_text": "ALLEVIATOR",
      "question": "In aviation, what specific control device is used to reduce the angle of attack"
    },
    {
      "id": 376,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "COMMITMENT",
      "question": "term describes a dedicated and firm pledge or promise to a cause,"
    }
  ]
}